<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bores Consultancy Ltd</title>
    <link>https://bores.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bores Consultancy Ltd</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; 2020 [Bores Ltd](https://bores.com) All Rights Reserved</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bores.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Morning</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/coffee/</guid>
      <description>Sorry about this, it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be more than a few seconds to redirect you. Looking forward to a good chat over coffee hopefully soon (coffee is optional for anyone other than me).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/consultancy/</guid>
      <description>Getting to a level of security suitable for your business requires a thorough understanding of the security domain, and a willingness to listen to your organisation. There is no one size fits all when designing appropriate security.</description>
<<<<<<< HEAD
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fail Safely</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/failsafe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/failsafe/</guid>
      <description>Our Fail Safely workshops, built on the Secure by Scenario framework, provide a cost-effect, immersive, team-based tabletop exercise to simultaneously educate staff and test incident response planning. Scenarios are immersive and open-ended, adapting to the actions your team declares rather than expecting everyone involved to follow a strict script which models a perfect reality.</description>
=======
>>>>>>> 4a7af8d21b24de5c85a338315a45c0cf6c4e246d
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Threat Modelling</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/classes/intro_threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/classes/intro_threat/</guid>
      <description>This two hour Introduction to Threat Modelling workshop walks through the fundamental approaches to threat modelling - focused on the threat, the impact, or the vulnerability. Exercises take you through a method from each approach, illustrating how to begin using threat modelling to build security into your design at a fundamental level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/media/</guid>
      <description>Over the years Chris and James have done a fair bit of writing, as well as providing interviews and expert commentary for the media. To request an interview, simply use our contact form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Playing at Security</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/playingatsecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/playingatsecurity/</guid>
      <description>You should be redirected to the worksheet form in a few seconds. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t (or don&amp;rsquo;t want to wait), you can click the link here to get there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pub Quiz</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/introquiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/introquiz/</guid>
      <description>You should be redirected to the quiz form in a few seconds. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t (or don&amp;rsquo;t want to wait), you can click the link here to get there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pub Quiz</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/speakerhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/speakerhub/</guid>
      <description>Something has gone wrong and you shouldn&amp;rsquo;t really be seeing this as it should be an immediate redirect, you can click the link here to get to your target.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Secure by Scenario</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/classes/scenario/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/classes/scenario/</guid>
      <description>This bespoke workshop involves initial consultation with your organisation to build out a tailored and realistic scenario. In a moderated workshop we will then work with groups of your people to run through the scenario in stages, establishing responses and communication flows, and helping you to prepare for the worst from every angle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Threat Modelling Workshops</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/tm-events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/tm-events/</guid>
      <description>Sorry about the delay in redirecting you. Unfortunately with the platform we use for ticketing, there isn&amp;rsquo;t the option to set pretty preview images like we can here so this is a bit of a workaround.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TM-002 Threat Modelling with the OWASP Top 10</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/classes/owasp_threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/classes/owasp_threat/</guid>
      <description>Focusing on the details of the OWASP Top 10, the list of the most commonly exploited web application vulnerabilities published by OWASP, this workshop goes through how to take a vulnerability list and adapt it for use in fast, effective threat modelling during your web application design process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 10 Trivia Quiz</title>
      <link>https://bores.com/owaspquiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bores.com/owaspquiz/</guid>
      <description>You should be redirected to the quiz form in a few seconds. If you aren&amp;rsquo;t (or don&amp;rsquo;t want to wait), you can click the link here to get there.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>